Description:
  Build the NativePHP application for the specified operating system and architecture.

Usage:
  native:build [options] [--] [<os> [<arch>]]

Arguments:
  os                    The operating system to build for (all, linux, mac, win)
  arch                  The Processor Architecture to build for (x64, x86, arm64)

Options:
      --publish         to publish the app
  -h, --help            Display help for the given command. When no command is given display help for the list command
      --silent          Do not output any message
  -q, --quiet           Only errors are displayed. All other output is suppressed
  -V, --version         Display this application version
      --ansi|--no-ansi  Force (or disable --no-ansi) ANSI output
  -n, --no-interaction  Do not ask any interactive question
      --env[=ENV]       The environment the command should run under
  -v|vv|vvv, --verbose  Increase the verbosity of messages: 1 for normal output, 2 for more verbose output and 3 for debug
